Contact

01100866990 (Mobile) muhammadalaa5@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/imhmdd (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Architectural Design Interior Design Design Research

Certifications

Data Analysis Professional Udacity Nanodegree

Data Analysis Challenger Track - FWD

Muhammad Alaa El-Deen

Personalized Ads Assessor at TELUS International Alexandria

Summary

My objectives are to develop my skills and gain more experience. I am looking forward to be working in an architectural firm where I can continue gaining knowledge and developing the technical skills I have gained throughout my studies. My goal is to improve my career in order to gain a better chance at being a member of the team that will give me the opportunity for continued professional growth, also improving myself at all times as I believe one should never stop learning as it is the best way to become successful in the future. Therefore I always strive towards self development in all aspects.

Experience

TELUS International
Personalized Ads Assessor
September 2021 - Present (4 months)
Alexandria, Egypt

Helping Companies to improve the searching/browsing experience by assessing the results that showed to the user based on the query they searched for.

Kamal Saad for paper products Cashier

June 2019 - September 2019 (4 months)

Alexandria, Egypt

- Process sales transactions
- Calculate the cost of products or services
- Accept payments
- Calculate and return change when required by the payment method
- Answer customer questions about products or services

Education

Alexandria University

Bachelor's degree, Architecture · (September 2016 - July 2021)